avocode.com 2019-12-19

# Avocode Privacy Policy (Effective from August 15, 2019)

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information when using our Service. Your information will not be shared or used by anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may use your Personal Information in order for you to use the Service and in order to make improvements from time to time. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy constitutes an integral part of our Terms of Service (the “ ** _Terms of Service_** ”). Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meanings as assigned to them in our Terms of Service, accessible at [https://avocode.com](https://avocode.com/).

## Definitions

  1.  ** _"Contact Information"_** means your name, your physical address, and your e-mail address.
  2.  ** _"Affiliates"_** means any parent, subsidiary, member, officer, director, employee, or agent of Avocode, Inc. or any company under common control with us.
  3.  ** _"Non-Personal Information"_** is information that does not personally identify an individual.
  4.  ** _"Personal Information"_** is information that could potentially identify an individual.
  5.  ** _"Financial Account Information"_** means your credit card number, credit card expiration date and credit card verification code, all with respect to one or more credit cards that you have the lawful right to use, and your bank account number, bank account title, bank name, branch location and routing number, all with respect to one or more accounts that you have the lawful right to access; provided “ **Financial Account Information** ” does not include the last four digits of your credit card number, which we retain for purposes of verifying User Account and User Account Information.
  6.  ** _"Transaction Information"_** means all information related to transactions that you conduct on the Service and your interactions with the Service.
  7.  ** _"User Account"_** means an account permitting access to the Service, with which is associated a user name and password.
  8.  ** _"User Account Information"_** means information that identifies you to the Service, including your user name, password, internet protocol address, and browser user agent information.
  9.  ** _"User Content"_** means images, designs, fonts, certain code templates, and other materials that you post to the Service.

## Information we collect

We collect the following types of Personal Information through the Service:

  * Contact information
  * Financial Account Information
  * Transaction Information
  * User Account Information
  * User Content

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Information, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Information to the Service, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Information may be transferred from your current location to our servers and the authorized third parties referred to herein.

## Computer information collected

  *  **Cookies:** Our Site uses **_“Cookies”_** to identify the areas of our Site that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data that may have a unique identifier stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser, or by e-mails we send to you, or on our web pages. We use Cookies to personalize the content that you see on our Site. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access many of the features on our Site correctly. We never place Personal Information in Cookies.
  *  **Third party tracking tools:** We also use third party tracking tools to improve the performance and features of our Site. These third party tracking tools are designed to collect only Non-Personal Information about your use of our Service. However, you understand that such tools are created and managed by parties outside our control. As such, we are not responsible for what information is actually captured by such third parties or how such third parties use and protect that information.
  *  **Remarketing tracking code:** We use Remarketing with Facebook Pixels and Google AdWords to advertise on third party sites to you after you visited our Site. We and our third party vendors, like Google, use first party Cookies (such as the Google Analytics Cookie) and third party Cookies (such as the DoubleClick Cookie) to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
  *  **Automatic information:** We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Site, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you're headed when you leave our Site. This information also includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your location, access times, your Internet provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our users to help improve our Site and the Service.

## How we use your information

We use the information we receive from you to:

  * Operate and improve the Service
  * Register your User Account and manage your payment plan, and authenticate your Financial Account Information
  * Customize our Site in accordance with your preferences, such as by making recommendations based on your history of content uploading
  * Share information with Affiliates or third party payment processors or hosting companies
  * Aggregate data
  * Target marketing and advertising campaigns
  * Target promotional offers to users
  * Provide technical support and customer service
  * Send you information relating to the Service, communicate with you about offers, promotions, rewards, and other news regarding the Service offered by us and our Affiliates
  * Protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity

## Financial Account Information

We may require your Financial Account Information for the purpose of purchasing a subscription plan to provide you with the Service. By submitting your Financial Account Information, you expressly consent to the sharing of your information with our affiliates, third-party payment processors, third parties that process online payments and provide technical, fraud prevention and banking infrastructure.

When you use a credit or debit card to make a purchase through our Site or Application, we provide your Financial Account Information to our third-party payment service providers to process your payments. We do not store any Financial Account Information ourselves. However, these third parties may store your Financial Account Information in accordance with their privacy policies which you should familiarize yourself with.

For information about the security of your Financial Account Information, see Section called “ **Storage and security** ” below.

## How we share your information

We may share your Personal Information, information in the “ **Computer information** ” section and Financial Account Information with third parties for the purpose of technical management of the Service, to facilitate the payment plans, to track critical retention metrics, and to perform marketing campaigns for Avocode. Your information may also be consolidated and anonymized into reports that may be sold to commercial third parties.

We may share Personal Information with our Affiliates. We may share your Financial Account Information with third parties as described in the section called “Financial Account Information” above.

We share Personal Information with third parties who provide services to us, such as data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and site analytics, as well as assistance with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own Cookies. We may also share Personal Information with independents third parties for the purpose of providing you with advertising materials of their services or products that may be targeted toward your interests. We and our third-party service providers, advertisers, and/or partners may also place web beacons for these third parties. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information to comply with laws and to respond to lawful requests and legal process, to protect the rights and property of Avocode, our agents and customers, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use, and in an emergency to protect the personal safety of Avocode, its customers, or any person.

We may disclose or transfer your Personal Information to a third party if we sell, transfer, divest, or disclose all or a portion of our business or assets to another company in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, transaction, or proceeding.

We may share aggregate statistical data for the improvement of services offered by our Sites. We may also share Non-Personal Information with third parties in our discretion, including to third party analytics sites in order to receive reports regarding our user base as a whole.

In the event that your Personal Information is to be shared in any manner other than as provided in our Privacy Policy, we shall provide you with notice of how your Personal Information will be shared and give you the opportunity to opt out. Please note that continued usage after such notice constitutes consent to the use of the Information in the manner provided in the notice.

## Accessing and correcting personal information

You may correct or update your Personal Information via your [Account’s ”Settings”](https://app.avocode.com/personal-account/profile/) section on the Site or Application. You may also send requests about your contact preferences or changes to your information, including requests to opt out of sharing your Personal Information with third parties, to our contact information below.You have the right to access your Personal Information and the right to object to the use of your Personal Information. If you desire to access your Personal Information in our possession, we encourage you to contact us at [compliance@avocode.com](mailto:compliance@avocode.com) and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.

You may close an account, but we will nevertheless retain your Personal Information in order to complete transactions, maintain records for the purpose of financial reporting, to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce agreements.

## Storage and security

The security of your information is a serious issue for us and we are committed to protect the information we receive from you. We use reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control. Notwithstanding such measures, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Service, including your Personal Information or Financial Account Information. We also are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

WE ASSUME NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION DUE TO ERRORS IN TRANSMISSION, UNAUTHORIZED THIRD-PARTY ACCESS, OR OTHER CAUSES BEYOND OUR CONTROL.

When your Financial Account Information is being transmitted to our Site or Application or through our Site or Application, it will be protected by encryption technology.

To clarify, Avocode does not itself store your Financial Account Information, and we do not have direct control over or responsibility for your Financial Account Information. We collect and process Financial Account Information from you using third party PCI-compliant service providers when you subscribe to the Service. Our contracts with third parties that receive your Financial Account Information require them to keep it secure and confidential. We will retain Personal Information only as long needed for our internal processes and to comply with applicable laws. We will then destroy or render unreadable any such information upon disposal.

You play an important role in keeping your Personal Information secure and you should not share your user name, password, or other security information for your Account with anyone. If we receive instructions using your user name and password, we will consider that you have authorized the instructions.

## Links to other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Protecting your child’s privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“ ** _Children_** ”).

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Children under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

## Our e-mail policy

We fully comply with national laws regarding SPAM. You may opt out of receiving promotional e-mails from us by following the instructions in the e-mails. If you opt out, we may still send non-promotional e-mails, such as e-mails concerning your Account or our ongoing business relations.

We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your e-mail address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.

## EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield framework

We comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of Personal Information from European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. We have certified to the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. We also remain responsible for any of your Personal Information that is shared under the Privacy Shield Onward Transfer Principle (the Onward Transfer Principle may be accessed at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=3-ACCOUNTABILITY-FOR-ONWARD-TRANSFER>) with third parties for external processing on our behalf, as described in the “How we share your information” section.

## Covered Entities

This certification applies to Avocode, Inc and Abdoc Technology s.r.o.

 **Compliance and cooperation with regulatory authorities**

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve your complaints about our collection or use of your Personal Information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us by filing the [Privacy Shield Complaint Form](https://avocode.com/privacy-shield-complaint-form) AND/OR contacting us at [compliance@avocode.com](mailto:compliance@avocode.com).

When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users.

We have further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, located in the United States. We commit to cooperate with and comply with the advice given by JAMS. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit (<https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of filing a complaint with JAMS are provided at no cost to you. In certain circumstances and for European Union individuals, the Privacy Shield Framework provides the right to invoke binding arbitration to resolve complaints not resolved by other means, as described in Annex I to the Privacy Shield Principles. If you meet these circumstances, please contact or visit JAMS (<https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>) for more information or to file a complaint.

We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

## Privacy policy updates

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace this Privacy Policy at any time. We will provide at least 14 days’ notice prior to any new terms taking effect. You understand that it is your obligation to make sure that the e-mail you provided is operational and that e-mails from us will not be redirected to your spam folder.

You are free to decide whether or not to accept a modified version of this Privacy Policy, but accepting this Policy, as modified, is required for you to continue using our Service. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any modified version of this Privacy Policy, your sole recourse is to terminate your use of the Service.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about accessing, changing, or deleting your Personal Information, please visit [https://avocode.com](https://avocode.com/) or contact us at [team@avocode.com](mailto:team@avocode.com).

If you have an inquiry regarding our privacy practices in relation to our Privacy Shield certification or desire to access your personal data in our possession, we encourage you to contact us at [compliance@avocode.com.](mailto:compliance@avocode.com)

For questions or opinions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at [team@avocode.com](mailto:team@avocode.com) or by postal mail at Avocode, Inc., 330 East 59th Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10022, USA.
